A Guide to the Virginia Hummel Papers 1830-1998
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Virginia Hummel Papers 1830-1998
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Ms98-014
3.0 cubic feet, 3 boxes, 318 folders
The Virginia Hummel collection was donated in April 1998 by Hummel's daughters, Mary Benton Hummel and Elizabeth Hancock. The collection was organized by Sarah Gouger, student assistant, and Laura Katz Smith, Manuscript Curator.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open to research.
Biographical/Historical Information
Hummel, born on September 28, 1916, was an English teacher with Blacksburg High School and an avid amateur historian of Blacksburg and Appalachian regional history. Much of the subject matter of the materials concerns the history of Blacksburg and Montgomery County, Virginia. Hummel died on May 19, 1998, at the age of 81.
Scope and Content Information
The Virginia Hummel collection consists of newspaper clippings, research notes, photographs, maps, and blueprints collected and created by Virginia Hummel of Blacksburg.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged according to date.
Contents List
- Box 1 1898-1993
  - Student Handbook of VPI, fourth edition 1898-99 (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Maps of Blacksburg 1900-01 (Box-folder 1-2)
  - "Bird's Eye view of Blacksburg, Va." (photograph) 1908 (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Map of portion of VPI campus 1908 (Box-folder 1-4)
  - Photocopied pictures of VPI campus and faculty 1929-32 (Box-folder 1-5)
  - VPI Commencement exercises 1930 (Box-folder 1-6)
  - "The Tattle Tale," Blacksburg High School's newspaper, Senior issue 1931 (Box-folder 1-7)
  - The Techgram 1932 (Box-folder 1-8)
  - Montgomery County History, written by Estelle B. Price 1940 (Box-folder 1-9)
  - Bulletin of the VPI Institute Historical index, 1872-1942 1942 (Box-folder 1-10)
  - History of Blacksburg, Va.; important dates compiled by Ralph Minthorne Brown 1942 (Box-folder 1-11)
  - Bulletin of the VPI engineering experiment station, series number 66, "The Punch Junes and other Appalachian Diamonds." 1944 (Box-folder 1-12)
  - Historical data book, VPI 1964 (Box-folder 1-13)
  - Blacksburg in 1898, by Rosanna Dawson 1978 (Box-folder 1-14)
  - Blueprint of the town of Blacksburg 1979 (Box-folder 1-15)
  - Townscape sites for historical markers 1982 (Box-folder 1-16)
  - Interviews with women graduates of Virginia Tech, by Mary Hill Rajas 1983 (Box-folder 1-17)
  - Photographs of Blacksburg houses and buildings 1987 (Box-folder 1-18)
  - Virginia Tech, Volume 14, Number 1 1991 (Box-folder 1-19)
  - Virginia Tech, Volume 16, Number 1 1993 (Box-folder 1-20)
  - Research and information on Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 1-21)
  - Greek organizations in Blacksburg: timeline, history, and housing n.d. (Box-folder 1-22)
  - Bulletin of the VPI, Historical Index 1872-1942 (Box-folder 1-23)
  - Notes; Monday Huckleberry, property, buildings in Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 1-24)
  - Historical pictures of Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 1-25)
  - Blacksburg history; notes, pictures, photographs n.d. (Box-folder 1-26)
  - Booklets of VPI: Doorways to Leadership, Historical Data Book, Information for prospective students n.d. (Box-folder 1-27)
  - Note cards with information about VPI campus, buildings, students and their majors n.d. (Box-folder 1-28)
  - Photocopied photographs and articles from The Bugle n.d. (Box-folder 1-29)
  - Photocopied photographs and articles from The 1903 Bugle n.d. (Box-folder 1-30)
  - Photocopied photographs from the 1917 Bugle n.d. (Box-folder 1-31)
  - Photocopied photographs and articles from the 1918 Bugle n.d. (Box-folder 1-32)
  - Photocopied photographs from the 1923 Bugle n.d. (Box-folder 1-33)
  - Photocopied photographs of VPI campus and professors n.d. (Box-folder 1-34)
  - Information regarding the buildings on VPI campus n.d. (Box-folder 1-35)
  - Historical maps of VPI campus n.d. (Box-folder 1-36)
  - Article, "Blacksburg was established back in 1798 when William Black deeded land to Town" n.d. (Box-folder 1-37)
  - In and Out of Context: Blacksburg Roots n.d. (Box-folder 1-38)
  - Newspaper briefs about Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 1-39)
  - History of Blacksburg, Va.; by Mrs. S.A. Wingard n.d. (Box-folder 1-40)
  - Notes; Bits and pieces of early Blacksburg history n.d. (Box-folder 1-41)
  - Photocopied photographs of buildings in Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 1-42)
  - Brochures, guides to Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 1-43)
  - Photocopied article, In Old Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 1-44)
  - Information on houses and buildings in Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 1-45)
  - Photocopied photographs of Blacksburg, 1900-1912 n.d. (Box-folder 1-46)
  - Notes on the history of Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 1-47)
  - Maps, diagrams of Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 1-48)
  - Montgomery County, Local History n.d. (Box-folder 1-49)
  - Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 1-50)
  - Article, Coal Miner's Day to honor Montgomery County heritage n.d. (Box-folder 1-51)
  - Cadet life during the first year of the Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College at Blacksburg, Va. by Harry D. Temple n.d. (Box-folder 1-52)
  - Notes from Harry Temple n.d. (Box-folder 1-53)
  - Photocopied notes from Harry Temple's Military History of VPI summer 1929 n.d. (Box-folder 1-54)
  - Photocopied, Donning the Blue and Gray by Harry D. Temple n.d. (Box-folder 1-55)
  - Photocopied, The VPI Cadet, by Harry D. Temple n.d. (Box-folder 1-56)
  - Article, "Christmas and the Battle of the Bulge," by Harry D. Temple n.d. (Box-folder 1-57)
  - Articles about the Huckelberry Railroad n.d. (Box-folder 1-58)
  - Article, "VPI History: the early days;" photocopied n.d. (Box-folder 1-59)
  - Professors of Division of Academic Science, Division of Agriculture, the Administrative organization of VPI; photocopied n.d. (Box-folder 1-60)
  - Articles and pamphlets on Solitude n.d. (Box-folder 1-61)
  - Drapers Meadow articles n.d. (Box-folder 1-62)
  - Drapers Meadow, Smithfield, and Blacksburg; by Harvey Lee Price and John P. Hale n.d. (Box-folder 1-63)
  - Smithfield Plantation, articles and pictures n.d. (Box-folder 1-64)
  - Brochure, The Price House and Garden Park n.d. (Box-folder 1-65)
  - Guides to Mountains in Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 1-66)
  - Maps and diagrams of Christiansburg, Patrick Henry Trail and the Huckleberry Line n.d. (Box-folder 1-67)
- Box 2 1830-1998, n.d.
  - Letter from John Brown requesting money, original and photocopied 1830 (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Land deed between David Buchauau and Solomon G. Barrick 1841 (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Copy of Elizabeth Evan's application for membership of the United Daughters of the Confederacy 1864 (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Certificate declaring J.B. Board judge as deemed by the governor 1873 (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Letter of declaration appointing G.B. Board judge of the county court of Roanoke 1873 (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Letter to G.B. Board from Geo. Steck and Co. informing him of their shipment 1884 (Box-folder 2-6)
  - Record of shipment of an upright piano by the Piedmont Air Line 1884 (Box-folder 2-7)
  - Deed between Francis Board and G.B. Board 1887 (Box-folder 2-8)
  - Envelope and stamps 1892 (Box-folder 2-9)
  - Apraisement of Property found in the Derrlling House of Mr. Mark G. Board 1898 (Box-folder 2-10)
  - Freight Bill from Norfolk and Western Railway Co. for W.R. Price 1898 (Box-folder 2-11)
  - Freight Bill fro Norfolk and Western Railway Co. for J. Price 1900 (Box-folder 2-12)
  - Letter from John Gordon to Miss Mary Price requesting renewal of magazine subscription 1914 (Box-folder 2-13)
  - Bill from Milling and Supply Company, Inc. to J.H. Price 1900 (Box-folder 2-14)
  - Weekly Times, photocopied 1937 (Box-folder 2-15)
  - Letter from the Commonwealth of Virginia department of Health Bureau of Vital Statistics to Local Registrars of Virginia 1945 (Box-folder 2-16)
  - Receipt of payment of $100,000 from Dr. Hummel to L.F. Wong 1946 (Box-folder 2-17)
  - Record of the Keister family written by John Taylor Keister 1946 (Box-folder 2-18)
  - Keister genealogy by John Taylor Keister and Nannie V. Sibold 1946 (Box-folder 2-19)
  - Price genealogy by J. Taylor Keister and Nannie V. Sibold 1948 (Box-folder 2-20)
  - Virginia Hummel's test and paper for Shakespeare, English 231 1950 (Box-folder 2-21)
  - Refunds from Montgomery Ward and Co. to Julia E. Price 1952 (Box-folder 2-22)
  - The National Bank of Blacksburg football schedule for Virginia Tech and Blacksburg High School 1953 (Box-folder 2-23)
  - Graduation Announcements 1953-62 (Box-folder 2-24)
  - Birth certificate for Edith Hunt 1960 (Box-folder 2-25)
  - Christmas card from Gene Mah to Virginia Hummel 1962 (Box-folder 2-26)
  - Lineage of Mayo Brodie's ancestral couple 1965 (Box-folder 2-27)
  - Certificate of Appreciation for Mr. B.L. Hummel, Sr. from the Children's Home Society of Virginia 1967 (Box-folder 2-28)
  - Letter to Mrs. Hummel from her cousin in law 1968 (Box-folder 2-29)
  - Diary of Rosanna Croy Dawson, Blacksburg, Va., 1860 list of pupils of William Dawson 1972 (Box-folder 2-30)
  - Calendar - The National Bank of Blacksburg 1973 (Box-folder 2-31)
  - Letter to Virginia Hummel from Margaret and Charles Wood describing visit to American Memorial Cemetary in Manilla, slides of Memorial, diagram of Memorial 1974 (Box-folder 2-32)
  - Article, "Antique Group hears talk on old Blacksburg homes" 1976 (Box-folder 2-33)
  - Birth announcement from Roy and Jane Holden about the birth of their grandson John Holden Boyenton 1977 (Box-folder 2-34)
  - Calendar from the National Bank of Blacksburg 1978 (Box-folder 2-35)
  - Some decendants of Col. William Jenkins Thomas, compiled by Conway Price, preliminary draft 1979 (Box-folder 2-36)
  - Calendars, the Town of Blacksburg, the National Bank of Blacksburg 1979-80 (Box-folder 2-37)
  - Some decendants of Giles Thomas, revolutionary soldier, compiled by W. Conway Price, Ph.D. 1979-80 (Box-folder 2-38)
  - Blacksburg Town Calendars 1981-83 (Box-folder 2-39)
  - "A History of the Blacksburg Presbyterian Church, It's first 50 years" by Ellison A. Smith 1982 (Box-folder 2-40)
  - The Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Fold Art Center Curator Work Sheet, information on the Painting "Blacksburg" by Lewis Miller 1984 (Box-folder 2-41)
  - A brief History from Early Days, photocopied 1984 (Box-folder 2-42)
  - Blacksburg Town Calendar 1984 (Box-folder 2-43)
  - A Community of Churches, A Comprehensive Guide to our area churches 1985 (Box-folder 2-44)
  - Letter to Mrs. Hummel from Joyce M. Martin regarding information about Martin's grandfather 1985 (Box-folder 2-45)
  - Blacksburg Town Calendars 1985-87 (Box-folder 2-46)
  - Correspondence between Virginia Hummel and and A.J. Gardner 1986 (Box-folder 2-47)
  - Centennial History, Luther Memorial Lutheran Church 1986 (Box-folder 2-48)
  - Article, "Independence, A.G. Smith lived 95 years to the fullest" 1986 (Box-folder 2-49)
  - The National Bank Calendar 1990 (Box-folder 2-50)
  - Town of Blacksburg, National Bank Calendars 1991 (Box-folder 2-51)
  - Information regarding a slide show by Virginia Hummel in an undisclosed location 1992 (Box-folder 2-52)
  - Poem, "From Xanadu to you or a Plague on Both their Houses" by Mary Benton Hummel 1995 (Box-folder 2-52)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1996 (Box-folder 2-53)
  - Obituary on Virginia Hummel in the Roanoke Times Current Section 1998 (Box-folder 2-54)
  - Poems written about "Uncle Sporty," Charles Owens n.d. (Box-folder 2-55)
  - Essay on Shakespeare's Othello by Virginia Hummel n.d. (Box-folder 2-56)
  - Essay on Shakespeare's Polonius by Virginia Hummel n.d. (Box-folder 2-57)
  - Essay on Prince Hal by Virginia Hummel n.d. (Box-folder 2-58)
  - Blacksburg Cemetary receipt, sympathy card, article about Mrs. Roop's 90th birthday n.d. (Box-folder 2-59)
  - Memories of Mattie Lamb Tucker n.d. (Box-folder 2-60)
  - Injuries, deaths, discharges, transfers of corporals and privates n.d. (Box-folder 2-61)
  - Miscellaneous notes, cards, and envelopes n.d. (Box-folder 2-62)
  - Prints of paintings of Carol Hoge: Thomas Conner House and Cabose Park n.d. (Box-folder 2-63)
  - History 3055, Civil War and Reconstruction class notes n.d. (Box-folder 2-64)
  - Stamps n.d. (Box-folder 2-65)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution; application for membership, eligibility forms, membership cards n.d. (Box-folder 2-66)
  - Births, deaths, marriages taken from the Bible n.d. (Box-folder 2-67)
  - Genealogy of Thomas Henderson's family and Colonel John Brown's family n.d. (Box-folder 2-68)
  - The Brown's of Roanoke, Va.; by Francis Parker Brown n.d. (Box-folder 2-69)
  - Pamphlet for Deacon Brodie's Tavern n.d. (Box-folder 2-70)
  - McGavock Family Genealogy n.d. (Box-folder 2-71)
  - Births, deaths, marriages of the Mayo family; photocopied from the family Bible n.d. (Box-folder 2-72)
  - Miscellaneous; personals, marriages, wedding, our town n.d. (Box-folder 2-72)
  - Otey family: genealogy, diary, article n.d. (Box-folder 2-73)
  - Blacksburg deeds n.d. (Box-folder 2-74)
  - Notes, doctors of Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 2-75)
  - Giles Thomas and Col. William Thomas, essays describing their lives n.d. (Box-folder 2-76)
  - Genealogy of various families in Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 2-77)
  - Map of Coleved Cemetary, Roanoke n.d. (Box-folder 2-78)
  - Genealogy of the Rovich family n.d. (Box-folder 2-79)
  - Evans family; marriages, births, deaths n.d. (Box-folder 2-80)
  - Births and deaths from people possible taken from headstones at a cemetary n.d. (Box-folder 2-81)
  - Virginia Hummel's family genealogy; interest in Blacksburg n.d. (Box-folder 2-82)
  - Kent family genealogy n.d. (Box-folder 2-83)
  - Letter describing lab desk n.d. (Box-folder 2-84)
  - Photocopied pictures of B.L. Hummel which appeared in the newspaper n.d. (Box-folder 2-85)
  - Portrait of an unknown man n.d. (Box-folder 2-86)
  - Mayo family history n.d. (Box-folder 2-87)
  - Last will and testament of James R. Kent n.d. (Box-folder 2-88)
  - Roy J. Holden, by Heath M. Robinson, photocopied n.d. (Box-folder 2-89)
  - Geology at VPI, photocopied pages from Mineral Industries Journal n.d. (Box-folder 2-90)
  - Mattie Tucker - where people live on Roanoke Street n.d. (Box-folder 2-91)
  - NSDAR Ancestral chart n.d. (Box-folder 2-92)
  - Letter certifying that Mattie Kelly is a registered voter n.d. (Box-folder 2-93)
  - Birthday card to Virginia Hummel from the fourth period class n.d. (Box-folder 2-94)
  - Photocopies of newspaper articles honoring Virginia Hummel n.d. (Box-folder 2-95)
  - Card expressing thanks to Virginia Hummel for all her help from the senior patrol of Troop 9 n.d. (Box-folder 2-96)
  - Good-bye card thanking Virginia Hummel for all her help Monday afternoons n.d. (Box-folder 2-97)
  - Negatives and photographs of various people n.d. (Box-folder 2-98)
  - Letters, order forms regarding Dayton M. Kohler's two volume set of "Master Plots" n.d. (Box-folder 2-99)
  - Calendar n.d. (Box-folder 2-100)
  - Thank you cards, valentines, from Elizabeth to Aunt Virginia n.d. (Box-folder 2-101)
  - Dorsetts help preserve area history n.d. (Box-folder 2-102)
  - Memorial Lutheran celebrates anniversary of organization n.d. (Box-folder 2-103)
  - Miscellaneous ink drawings n.d. (Box-folder 2-104)
  - Congratulations card from John, Sue Ellen and Elizabeth n.d. (Box-folder 2-105)
  - Hummel family personal n.d. (Box-folder 2-106)
  - Historical facts about Blacksburg, Va. n.d. (Box-folder 2-107)
  - Article on death of G. Burke Johnston; poem "You are old, Father Johnston" by Bill Lipscomb n.d. (Box-folder 2-108)
  - Notes on history of churches in Montgomery County n.d. (Box-folder 2-109)
  - Hummel genealogy n.d. (Box-folder 2-110)
  - Genealogy of the Evans family n.d. (Box-folder 2-111)
  - Advertisement for men's shoes by Rice and Hutchins, Inc. n.d. (Box-folder 2-112)
  - Notes on family, children, ages, map of property lines n.d. (Box-folder 2-113)
  - Linkous - Kipps family n.d. (Box-folder 2-114)
  - Broce family n.d. (Box-folder 2-115)
  - Christ Church history n.d. (Box-folder 2-116)
  - Eulogy for Evans Gardner, professor of horticultural science at NSCU n.d. (Box-folder 2-117)
  - Picture of the members of the Methodist Church Sunday School taken in 1934, photocopied n.d. (Box-folder 2-118)
  - Memorial to Roy Jay Holden n.d. (Box-folder 2-119)
  - Notes on deeds n.d. (Box-folder 2-120)
  - The intellectual history of modern Europe, syllabus, class notes n.d. (Box-folder 2-121)
  - Drawing of the locations of graves in an undisclosed cemetary n.d. (Box-folder 2-122)
  - Blacksburg, Va., Residents 1819-40, 1845-46, 1948-54, 1871-72, 1881-88; compiled by Ralph M. Brown n.d. (Box-folder 2-123)
  - In Rememberance, In Loving Memory cards n.d. (Box-folder 2-124)
  - Town of Blacksburg plans n.d. (Box-folder 2-125)
  - Map collection n.d. (Box-folder 2-126)
- Box 3 1954-1997, n.d.
  - Norfolk - Virginia Pilot article, Camp Carysbrook, A Tradition Fostered by Preston Sisters 1954 (Box-folder 3-1)
  - A note to Stonegate homeowners from McBryde-Stonegate-Longview homeowners association 1965 (Box-folder 3-2)
  - UVa Students Walk Out, article from the Richmond Times Dispatch 1969 (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Article, "Delivered 10,000 Babies for sure, Doctor says;" Roanoke Times 1971 (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Article, "Rats, Parades, and Sham Battles" 1971 (Box-folder 3-5)
  - Context Special Issue, centennial photo album 1972 (Box-folder 3-6)
  - General Assembly of North Carolina, Session 1975, House Joint Resolution 311 1975 (Box-folder 3-7)
  - Article; "From Wells and Plank Sidewalks, Blacksburg's Changed" 1976 (Box-folder 3-8)
  - Articles; "History of Founding of Tech," News Messenger 1976 (Box-folder 3-9)
  - Articles from the Bicentennial Edition of the News Messenger, July 1, 1976 (Box-folder 3-10)
  - "Touring Historic Homes in the county," The News Messenger 1976 (Box-folder 3-11)
  - Article; "Walnut Springs Rich in History" 1976 (Box-folder 3-12)
  - Context; The VPI and SU Quarterly Magazines 1977 (Box-folder 3-13)
  - Article; "They don't make houses like they used to" 1979 (Box-folder 3-14)
  - Articles and pictures from the News Messenger. Bicentennial Celebration, photocopied 1979 (Box-folder 3-15)
  - The News Messenger, Your Guide to Montgomery County 1981 (Box-folder 3-16)
  - Interviews with women graduates of Virginia Tech, by Anne H. Giles 1983 (Box-folder 3-17)
  - "Decking the Halls, Colonial Christmas being prepared," article 1985 (Box-folder 3-18)
  - Article, "Faded Glory is well-Remembered," pamphlet about Yellow Sulfur Springs 1985 (Box-folder 3-19)
  - Article; "Not Plush, perhaps, but practical;" about rent a wreck 1985 (Box-folder 3-20)
  - Article on James Robertson, Civil War professor at VPI 1985 (Box-folder 3-21)
  - Article; "Christiansburg depot recognized by state landmark register" 1985 (Box-folder 3-22)
  - Article; "Details, Details: Quick what was Christiansburg once called?" 1985 (Box-folder 3-23)
  - Blacksburg annual report 1985 (Box-folder 3-24)
  - Article; "King Coal once held court in Montgomery County mines" 1986 (Box-folder 3-25)
  - Article; "Messenger has a long history" 1986 (Box-folder 3-26)
  - Article; "Society is digging into Valley's Past, archaeological dig in the New River Valley" 1987 (Box-folder 3-27)
  - Letter from Margaret and Charles Wood to Evans kin about the memorials fund of Blacksburg Baptist church 1987 (Box-folder 3-28)
  - Article; "University receives $10 million gift" 1987 (Box-folder 3-29)
  - Article; "Blacksburg history" 1987 (Box-folder 3-30)
  - Article; Whence Hokie, Whither Hokie, Virginia Tech, Vol. 9, No. 3 1987 (Box-folder 3-31)
  - Article; "Stonecutters have left part of their lives on every rock on every campus building," Virginia Tech Vol. 9, No. 3 1987 (Box-folder 3-32)
  - Article; "Irises and History kept alive," The News Messenger 1988 (Box-folder 3-33)
  - Articles describing the iris garden at the Price House 1988 (Box-folder 3-34)
  - Virginia Tech Alumni Association Annual Report 1988-89 (Box-folder 3-35)
  - Mary Tom Long 1991 (Box-folder 3-36)
  - Spectrum insert, information on VPI 1991 (Box-folder 3-37)
  - Article; "One Man Show, Governor Doug Wilder of Va." 1991 (Box-folder 3-38)
  - New River Current, Roanoke Times and World News, Tuesday, Feb. 5, 1991 (Box-folder 3-39)
  - Article; "Students work to aid Solitude" 1991 (Box-folder 3-40)
  - Article; "The Thomas Conner Controversy" 1991-92 (Box-folder 3-41)
  - Article; "Threads of History, New River Current, Roanoke Times and World News" 1992 (Box-folder 3-42)
  - Article; "If Walls could Talk: Last rooms at Fabled Hotel site slip away" 1992 (Box-folder 3-43)
  - Virginia Hummel's nomination for the 1992 Governor's Award for Volunteering Excellence 1992 (Box-folder 3-44)
  - Roanoke Times and World News, Christiansburg Bicentennial 1992 (Box-folder 3-45)
  - A Game for Bragging Rights, the UVA vs. VT football game, photocopied 1992 (Box-folder 3-46)
  - Article; "Exams, homework soon may be passe in Fairfax" 1992 (Box-folder 3-47)
  - William Addison Caldwell Lange Dedication 1993 (Box-folder 3-48)
  - Article; "Seperate treasures," Roanoke Times and World News 1993 (Box-folder 3-49)
  - Letter to James L. Clark to Mr. Alfred Smith regarding dedication of Clark's Ph.D. dissertation to his high school teachers 1993 (Box-folder 3-50)
  - Department of Veterans Affairs marital status questionnaire 1994 (Box-folder 3-51)
  - Southeast Registrars Association newsletter 1994 (Box-folder 3-52)
  - President's Report, Virginia Tech 1994-95 (Box-folder 3-53)
  - Article; "Blacksburg Council approves Brush Mountain Subdivision, Taking a trail into the past" 1995 (Box-folder 3-54)
  - Article; "Ancient Syrian city, regulated to myth, is a reality" 1995 (Box-folder 3-55)
  - Articles; Egyptian pyramids and tombs discovered 1995 (Box-folder 3-56)
  - Article; "Re-created Mayflower to make new voyage" 1995 (Box-folder 3-57)
  - Article; "Mutual respect learned in the hills of Greece" 1995 (Box-folder 3-58)
  - Virginia Tech, Vol. 15, No. 2 1995 (Box-folder 3-59)
  - Article; "The Red Sea seems to make a habit of parting" 1995 (Box-folder 3-60)
  - Article; "Keeper of the Gate," Roanoke Times and World News 1995 (Box-folder 3-61)
  - Virginia Tech, Vol. 18, No. 1 1995 (Box-folder 3-62)
  - Articles containing information on Dr. Harvey Black 1995 (Box-folder 3-63)
  - Department of English newsletter, A Feast of Words 1995 (Box-folder 3-64)
  - New River Valley, Current Business 1995 (Box-folder 3-65)
  - Articles relating to the Aug. 9 shooting of Maurice Taylor 1995 (Box-folder 3-66)
  - Article; "Flood Victims get $23 million, Gov. Allen requests federal help" 1995 (Box-folder 3-67)
  - Article; "Getting to the core of the corps, from Harry Temple's The Bugles Echo" 1996 (Box-folder 3-68)
  - History lives thanks to the Cadets 1996 (Box-folder 3-69)
  - Articles; "Local Doctors face tax evasion charges" 1996 (Box-folder 3-70)
  - New River Current, The Roanoke Times, End of an Era 1997 (Box-folder 3-71)
  - Articles describing the German Club's Midwinter's Dance n.d. (Box-folder 3-72)
  - Articles describing items in Special Collections n.d. (Box-folder 3-73)
  - Article; "Bridge forms Tech 'Portal,' opposing Bridge across the mall" n.d. (Box-folder 3-74)
  - Five Chimneys, A documentation and proposal by Dan Pezzoni n.d. (Box-folder 3-75)
  - Mary Draper Ingles, Pioneer Heroine n.d. (Box-folder 3-76)
  - White Sulfur Springs Resort n.d. (Box-folder 3-77)
  - Hunting for History, Architect completes Montgomery Survey n.d. (Box-folder 3-78)
  - Article; "Someone's hero: Mary Benton Hummel" n.d. (Box-folder 3-79)
  - Miss BHS '53 gets center stage again n.d. (Box-folder 3-80)